https://www.binaryminds.com/contact/privacy-policy.cfm

Username
Password
Please email us if you forgot your password.
Binary Minds Privacy Policy
This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their
'Personally identifiable information' (PII) is being used online. PII, as used in US privacy law
and information security, is information that can be used on its own or with other information to
identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context.
Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect,
use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website.
What personal information do we collect from the people that visit our website?
When submitting an inquiry on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name,
email address, phone number or other details so we can contact you and answer your questions.
When do we collect information?
We collect information from you when you fill out our inquiry form or when accessing the customer portal.
How do we use your information?
We may use the information we collect from you when you submit an inquiry or sign up for our newsletter to
quickly process your transactions.
How do we protect visitor information?
Our website is scanned on a regular basis for security holes and known vulnerabilities in order to make your
visit to our site as safe as possible. We use regular Malware Scanning. Your personal information is
contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special
access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.
In addition, all sensitive/credit information you supply is encrypted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology.
We implement a variety of security measures when a user enters, submits, or accesses their information to
maintain the safety of your personal information.
All transactions are processed through a gateway provider and are not stored or processed on our servers.
Do we use 'cookies'?
Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive
through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site's or service provider's systems to recognize
your browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we use cookies to help us remember and
process the items in your shopping cart. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on
previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use
cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer
better site experiences and tools in the future.
We use cookies to:
Understand and save user's preferences for future visits.
Keep track of advertisements.
Compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interactions in order to offer better site experiences and tools
in the future. We may also use trusted third party services that track this information on our behalf.
You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all
cookies. You do this through your browser (like Internet Explorer) settings. Each browser is a little different,
so look at your browser's Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.
Disabling cookies will not affect the user experience. However, the customer portal will not function properly.
Third Party Disclosure
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information.
Third party links
We do not include or offer third party products or services on our website.
Google
We adhere to Google's advertising policy.
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google's use of the
DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our site and other
sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the
Google ad and content network privacy policy.
We have implemented the following:
Google Display Network Impression Reporting
Demographics and Interests Reporting
DoubleClick Platform Integration
We along with third-party vendors, such as Google use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies)
and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) or other third-party identifiers together to compile
data regarding user interactions with ad impressions, and other ad service functions as they relate to our website.
Opting out:
Users can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Settings page. Alternatively,
you can opt out by visiting the Network Advertising initiative opt out page or permanently using the
Google Analytics Opt Out Browser add on.
California Online Privacy Protection Act
CalOPPA is the first state law in the nation to require commercial websites and online services to post a privacy policy.
The law's reach stretches well beyond California to require a person or company in the United States
(and conceivably the world) that operates websites collecting personally identifiable information from
California consumers to post a conspicuous privacy policy on its website stating exactly the information
being collected and those individuals with whom it is being shared, and to comply with this policy. -
See more at: California Online Privacy Protection Act (CalOPPA)
According to CalOPPA we agree to the following:
Users can visit our site anonymously. Once this privacy policy is created, we will add a link to it on our home page,
or as a minimum on the first significant page after entering our website. Our Privacy Policy link includes the word
'Privacy', and can be easily be found on the page specified above. Users will be notified of any privacy policy
changes on our Privacy Policy Page. Users are able to change their personal information by emailing us, calling us,
logging in to their account, or by sending us a ticket.
How does our site handle do not track signals?
We honor do not track signals and do not track, plant cookies, or use advertising when a Do Not Track (DNT) browser mechanism is in place.
Does our site allow third party behavioral tracking?
It's also important to note that we do not allow third party behavioral tracking.
COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)
When it comes to the collection of personal information from children under 13, the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) puts parents in control. The Federal Trade Commission, the nation's consumer protection agency, enforces the COPPA Rule, which spells out what operators of websites and online services must do to protect children's privacy and safety online.
We do not specifically market to children under 13.
Fair Information Practices
The Fair Information Practices Principles form the backbone of privacy law in the United States and the concepts they
include have played a significant role in the development of data protection laws around the globe. Understanding the
Fair Information Practice Principles and how they should be implemented is critical to comply with the various privacy
laws that protect personal information. In order to be in line with Fair Information Practices we will notify the users via email or in site
notification should a breach occur.
CAN SPAM Act
The CAN-SPAM Act is a law that sets the rules for commercial email, establishes requirements for commercial messages,
gives recipients the right to have emails stopped from being sent to them, and spells out tough penalties for violations.
We collect your email address in order to:
Send information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.
Market to our mailing list or continue to send emails to our clients after the original transaction has occurred.
To be in accordance with CANSPAM we agree to the following:
NOT use false, or misleading subjects or email addresses
Identify the message as an advertisement in some reasonable way
Include the physical address of our business or site headquarters
Monitor third party email marketing services for compliance, if one is used.
Honor opt-out/unsubscribe requests quickly
Allow users to unsubscribe by using the link at the bottom of each email
If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you can follow the instructions at the bottom of each email.
and we will promptly remove you from ALL correspondence.
Contacting Us
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.
